// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let que2 = [
    {
      numb: 1,
      question: "CSS stands for -",
      answer: "Cascading style sheets",
      options: [
        "Cascade style sheets",
        "Color and style sheets",
        "Cascading style sheets",
        "None of the above"
      ]
    },
      {
      numb: 2,
      question: "Which if the following CSS function allows us to perform calculations?",
      answer: "calc() function",
      options: [
        "calc() function",
        "calculator() function",
        "calculate() function",
        "cal() function"
      ]
    },
   
    {
      numb: 3,
      question: " How can you add a hover effect to an element in CSS?",
      answer: ":hover",
      options: [
        ".hover",
        "#hover",
        "hover: true;",
        ":hover"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 4,
      question: "What is the default value of the display property in CSS?",
      answer: "block",
      options: [
        "inline",
        "block",
        "offline",
        "None of these"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 5,
      question: "Which css property is used to specify transparency of an element?",
      answer: "opacity",
      options: [
        "filter",
        "visibility",
        "filter",
        "opacity"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 6,
      question: "Which CSS property is used to control the spacing between lines of text?",
      answer: " line-height ",
      options: [
        "letter-spacing ",
        "text-spacing ",
        "line-height ",
        "text-line-height "
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 7,
      question: "Which property is used to create rounded corners for an element?",
      answer: "border-radius ",
      options: [
        "border-style ",
        "border-radius ",
        "border-width ",
        " border-color "
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 8,
      question: "What is the default position value of an element in CSS?",
      answer: "static ",
      options: [
        " static ",
        "relative ",
        "absolute ",
        " fixed "
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 9,
      question: "Which property is used to change the text size of an element?",
      answer: "font-size ",
      options: [
        " text-size ",
        "font-size ",
        "text-style ",
        "size "
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 10,
      question: "Which property is used to add a background image?",
      answer: "background-image",
      options: [
        "background-color ",
        "color ",
        "background-image",
        "image-background "
      ]
    },
      
  ];